

LUIS CARLOS PEREZ

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER

CONTACT

+36 30 528 7465 LUISCARLOS3106@GMAIL.COM

SOCIAL MEDIA

LINKEDIN:

LINKEDIN.COM/IN/LUIS-CARLOS-PEREZ-3B3195A6

FACEBOOK: @LUIS CARLOS PEREZ

INSTAGRAM: @LUISK3106

PROFILE

During my formative years, I've had the opportunity to live in different countries like Dominican Republic, Hungary and Spain, gaining many assets and experiences including personal growth, global perspective, and multiculturism.

Always passionate about technology and currently graduated from "Ironhack", an intensive learning project specialized in programming. Mastering programming technologies like Node.js, ES6, Express, and HTML & CSS, I belief in constant education development.

EXPERIENCE

BARISTA

STARBUCKS | MAR 2016 - JUN 2017

• Bring the best services and experiences to costumers

VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE

TECHO | JUN 2014 - JUL 2014

Build houses for the poor in Guatemala

EDUCATION

WEB DEVELOPMENT

IRONHACK MADRID | 2017 - 2017 - TECHNOLOGIES: JAVASCRIPT, HTML5, CSS3 AND THE MEAN STACK

MANAGEMENT WITH SPECIALISATION IN ARTS

IBS BUDAPEST | 2015 - 2017

- GAIN KNOWLEDGE OF HISTORY, FUNDING, OWNERSHIP AND CREATION OF ARTS, INCLUDING THE MUSIC INDUSTRY PLUS GENERAL MANAGEMENT ISSUES

SKILLS

- JavaScript
- Node.js
- Angular4
- Express.js
- MongoDB

- ES6
- JQuery
- HTML5
- CSS
- Web Development

AWARDS

AASCA MUSIC FESTIVAL

MOST OUTSTANDING GUITAR DUET DEC 2014

LANGUAGES

- Spanish
- Hungarian

English